healthplans.com 2014-05-17

# Privacy Policy | HealthPlans.com

**INTRODUCTION**  
HealthPlans.com (herein referred to as "we", "us" or "our") is committed ensuring the privacy and security of each user that visits our website. This privacy statement covers our website www.HealthPlans.com. We consider your privacy a very important issue, so we design and operate our services with the protection of your privacy as a primary concern. This privacy policy outlines the types of personal information we gather when you use our services, as well as efforts we make to safeguard it.

**CONTACT INFORMATION**  
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should first send an email to [contact@healthplans.com](mailto:contact@healthplans.com). You can also contact us via regular mail at: HealthPlans.com, 3301 NE 1st Avenue, PH4, Miami, FL 33137.

If you are a California resident and would like to request certain information regarding the disclosure of your personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes, please submit your request by writing us, calling us or emailing us using the contact information listed above. 

**COOKIES**  
A "cookie" is a test file that is placed in the browser files of your computer when you visit a website. The cookie enables us to relate your use of our website to information that you specifically and knowingly provided to us. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service and to provide content we believe would be of interest to you. Additionally we track usage statistics to better understand how people interact with our site. Cookies do not collect personally identifiable information; the information collected is in an aggregate, non-identifiable form. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information. Also, a cookie provided by a third party partner of ours will be placed on your computer when you click on an advertisement placed by that third party partner. This is done so that future advertisements can be targeted to you based on the advertisements clicked on by you in the past. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. We also will place a pixel provided by a third party partner on your computer to track the number of end-user conversions we obtain from our advertising. 

**PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**  
Personally identifiable information ("PII") is information that identifies you, is generally not available to the public, and may include information about your family as well as you personally. We collect PII that you provide us through interaction with our website in order to provide you the service(s) we offer. You are not obligated to provide us PII that we request, however, if you do not provide us with certain information, we may not be able to respond to your requests, process your applications or otherwise conduct the business contemplated between you and us. For all insurance quote requests we collect personal contact information including name, telephone number, mailing address, email address, gender, birthday and marital status. For life insurance quotes we may collect health information including family history, medications and existing conditions. 

**MINORS**  
Our website and services are not directed toward individuals who are under sixteen (16) years of age ("Minors") nor do we knowingly collect information from Minors. 

**USE OF INFORMATION**  
By filling out information on our website as part of a request for information about insurance policies and quotations, you authorize us to provide that information, including any health information, to various insurance companies, insurance agents and other related third parties that participate in our insurance quote network (collectively "Insurance Providers"). The Insurance Providers may provide your personal information to their insurance carriers, suppliers and other related vendors in order to generate price quotations and information relevant to insurance policies that you have requested, and the Insurance Providers may use the information to contact you directly with quotations by means of telephone, fax, and email, even if you have registered your phone number(s) on local and/or national no-call lists. You further acknowledge and agree that each Insurance Provider that receives your quote request from this website or from our affiliates may confirm your information through the use of a consumer report, which may include among other things, your driving record and/or credit score. For purposes of faxing, it is understood that Insurance Providers have an established business relationship with each user of this website, if required to comply with the then current law. 

We use reasonable commercial efforts to ensure that the Insurance Providers are obligated to protect your PII to at least the degree established in this policy. Additionally, it is our policy to require Insurance Providers to use commercially reasonable means to secure the receipt and processing of your PII.

You should be aware that after an Insurance Provider contacts you directly, any information you provide to the Insurance Provider, which may be the same as or similar to the PII you submitted to us through this website, will no longer be covered by this policy. In such cases, you should verify the individual Insurance Provider's privacy policies and practices. We have no control over these Insurance Providers and their practices and cannot and will not be responsible or liable, financial or otherwise, for their respective privacy policies and practices. Also be aware that the Insurance Providers may use the PII they acquire from this website in connection with other information they acquire about you (from other sources that have collected PII about you such as credit reporting companies, etc.) as well as information you provide them directly. We cannot and will not be responsible or liable, financial or otherwise, for any of the PII that you provide directly to Insurance Providers after the Insurance Provider contacts you or that they acquire from sources other than this website. 

We may also share your PII with the following types of entities and/or under the following circumstances: 

We may also use a third party ad network to help present advertisements on this website. Third-party ad serving enables us to target advertisements to you for products and services you might be interested in. These third party network advertisers, along with other advertisers and sponsors on the website, may use cookies, web beacons (also called single pixel gifs or action tags) or similar technologies (and, in the case of cookies, access them on your computer if you choose to have cookies enabled in your browser) to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicated advertisements. In doing so, the provider collects non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed and other clickstream data. The use of third party cookies, web beacons and similar technologies by these ad network providers is governed by each third party's specific privacy policy, not this one. Please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/> to learn more about the information collection practices and "opt-out" procedures of third party ad networks we may use. 

**INFORMATION FROM PUBLIC SOURCES**  
There is no way for you to access or update your information once a request is submitted. If you make a mistake in a request, you can re-submit your information in full. If you no longer want to receive correspondence regarding insurance quotes, you need to take action directly by contacting the respective Insurance Provider(s) that contact you and ask them to no longer contact you. We will not sell, rent or disclose your PII to third parties for purposes of their own marketing campaigns except as authorized in this policy. 

We may provide your PII to, or permit access to it by, our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, vendors and/or service providers for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf, or where such access is incidental to their providing assistance to us. In such cases, we expect these parties to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this privacy policy. 

We reserve the right to disclose your PII as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a court order, legal process or judicial proceeding served on us. 

**SECURITY**  
The security of your PII is important to us. While we utilize commercially reasonable measures to protect your PII, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. By visiting website and providing us with your PII, you acknowledge that you understand these risks exist and agree that you are assuming responsibility for these risks. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can send an email to us at [contact@healthplans.com](mailto:contact@healthplans.com). 

**AFFILIATED AND OTHER WEBSITES AND ADVERTISEMENTS**  
This privacy policy applies to websites and services that are owned and operated by HealthPlans.com. We do not exercise control over the websites of third parties that you may link to or view as part of a frame on a page on this website. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data, or solicit personally identifiable information from you. We are not responsible or liable, financial or otherwise, for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party. You should always be careful in how you use and share any sensitive personal information with any third party. 

**LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES**  
Our website may contain links to other websites that we believe may be beneficial to our users. We are not responsible or liable, financially or otherwise, for the privacy policies or practices of these sites. 

**CHANGES IN THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT**  
If we change our privacy policy, we will post the changes directly to this privacy statement, post a notice on our home page, and any other places we deem appropriate, so that you are aware of said changes. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. 

**Opt-Out, Your Choices and Changing Information You Provided to Us**  
You may choose whether or not you receive communications from us as follows. You may also opt out or change or modify information you have previously provided to us by contacting us by doing any one of the following: 

  * Marketing Email Opt-out: Each of our marketing email communications includes an opt-out link. You may click on that link and opt out from receiving marketing email.
  * Refusing Cookies: You can adjust your browser settings to opt out of the use of cookies by having your browser disable cookies. Look for the cookie options in your browser in the Options or Preferences menu.
  * Send an email to us at: [contact@healthplans.com](mailto:contact@healthplans.com)
  * Send a letter to: HealthPlans.com, 3301 NE 1st Avenue, PH4, Miami, FL 33137

If you have any questions about our site, services, and company policies or procedures, please contact us at HealthPlans.com's "Contact Us"
